viddsee.com 2016-11-18

# Privacy Policy | Viddsee

## Privacy

This Privacy Policy describes how Viddsee Pte Ltd ("We," "Our" or "Viddsee") collects, uses and shares your information on Viddsee.com (the "Viddsee Site"), related domains (including Viddsee BUZZ, Viddsee Creator), mobile applications and television applications (collectively, the "Viddsee Service"). Use of the Viddsee Service is subject to our Terms of Use.

### What information do we collect?

Non-identifying information. We obtain non-identifying information such as age, gender, country during registration. We also obtain non-identifying information by collecting data on your use of Viddsee Service, such as time and duration of use and frequency of use.

Identifiable information. We obtain identifiable information such as your name, email address during registration. You do not have to provide such personal information to us, but in that case, certain features of Viddsee Service may not be available to you.

We also have presences on prominent social networking sites. It is completely optional for you to be involved on these sites, but if you do participate (by leaving a comment or liking our page), we may have access to your personal information depending on your privacy settings.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information We collect from you may be used in the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs

To improve our products, services or content  
We continually strive to improve our offerings based on the information and feedback We receive from you

To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Viddsee Service feature

To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide during registration may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your registration, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. By accepting this privacy policy, you agree to receive the aforementioned information from us.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, We include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Despite these efforts, please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We want you to feel confident using Viddsee Service but We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers’ hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites’ or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about traffic and interaction so that We can offer better experiences and tools in the future.

### Do you use log data?

Yes. When you use Viddsee Service, whether as a registered or non-registered user, our servers may record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a content (such information to be known as "Log Data"). This Log Data may include information relating to your browser type, content pages of our Viddsee Service that you visit and your internet protocol address.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Viddsee Service, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when We believe such release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety, or in connection with a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, reorganization, dissolution or similar event. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, We may include or offer third party products, services or content on our Viddsee Service. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, We seek to protect the integrity of our Viddsee Service and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Reviewing or updating your information

You may review, update or have us delete your personal information by contacting us at the contact details below. However, do note that if you have us completely delete all such information, we will not be able to keep your account with us. We may also retain an archived copy of your personal information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

### Your consent

By using our Viddsee Service, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If We decide to change our Privacy Policy, We will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the date below. We recommend that you check our Privacy Policy from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 18 September 2014.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

www.viddsee.com   
#26-04, International Plaza,   
10, Anson Road   
Singapore 079903
